Guide to the Gerard Salton papers
Salton, Gerard papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Gerard Salton papers.
16-13-2908
Gerard Salton
100 cubic ft.
Correspondence, subject files, videocassettes, notebooks, manuscripts
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Subject files, correspondence, class notebooks, videocassettes, reprints, and other papers and records deriving from Salton's work in text processing, information retrieval, and computer science.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Professor of Computer Science, Cornell University. Salton has worked in the areas of natural language text processing, automatic text processing, and informational retrieval; editor-in-chief, Association for Computing Machinery Communications; Guggenheim Fellow, 1963.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Subject files, correspondence, class notebooks, videocassettes, reprints, and other papers and records deriving from Salton's work in text processing, information retrieval, and computer science.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Salton, Gerard.; Association for Computing Machinery
Subjects:
Computer science--Study and teaching.--New York (State)--Ithaca.; Text processing (computer science).; Information storage and retrieval systems.; Computers--Study and teaching.; Information science--Study and teaching.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Biographical
  - Biographical Information (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Series II. Correspondence
  - A-AM, 1971-1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ocor Biographics (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - AAAS - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1971-1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - ACM - Association for Computing Machinery, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Feb. 19, 1976 newsletter responses plus letter to the council regarding responses, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Feb. 1976 ACM letter, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - June 1976 ACM membership letter, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - June 28, 1976 ACM newsletter responses, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - ACM Council - Jim Adam's, 1972-1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ACM Council Letter, 5-21-76 RE: JAM, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - ACM Council - Chapter Correspondence, 1972-1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Oct. 1976 ACM Meeting letters and responses, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - ACM Letter - Feb. 1977 meeting, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 1977 ACM Computer Science Conference, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - ACM letter, June 1977, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - ACM letter, Nov. 1977, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Adams, Scott, 1969-1973 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - AM, 1971-1977 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Aronson, Fred, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - ARPA, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - ASIS - American Society for Information Science, 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - ASIS, 1971-1977 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - SLIB (all correspondence), 1969-1974 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Attari, Frankel, and Stein paper, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - BA, 1971-1977 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Baber, F.T., 1968-1971 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Battelle, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - BE, 1971-1977 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Beeri, Mr. C., 1974 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Belzer, Jack, 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Bergmark, Donna, 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Bering, Dr. Edgar A., Jr., 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - BI-BO, 1970-1977 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Board of Visitors, School of Information Studies - Syracuse University, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Book Orders, 1967-1975 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Book Releases, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Boothroyd Agency, 1971-1976 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Borko, Proffessor Harold, 1971-1977 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - BR, 1971-1977 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - British Computer Society, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Brooks, Fred - AD White Professorship, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - CA, 1971-1977 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Special CACM articles, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - CE-CL, 1971-1977 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Charmonman, Sak, 1972-1975 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Clepper, Mr. Peter A., 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Cranfield Project, 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Cleverdon, C. W., 1969-1977 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - CO, 1971-1977 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Colbans, Herbert, 1970-1976 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Cohen, Helen, 1974-1977 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Coling, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Computer World, 1973-1977 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Computing Reviews, 1971-1974 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Computers and the Humanities, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Cooper, 1970-1977 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Crawford, Bob, 1970-1976 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Cuadra, C., 1970-1975 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - DA, 1971-1978 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - DE-DEM, 1971-1977 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Dell, W.R. - Britannica Book of the Year, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - DEN-DEU, 1972-1977 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - DI, 1970-1977 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Dobis, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Dorethy, Barry C. - ACM ed. Staff, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - EA-EM, 1971-1977 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - ECPD, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Elias, Arthur W., 1969-1975 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - EN, 1971-1977 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Engineering - Cornell Quarterly, Donald Berth, 1969-1973 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Engineering Library, 1968-1972 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Even, Shimon, 1972-1975 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - FA, 1971-1977 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - FE-FI, 1971-1977 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Finerman, A., 1969-1977 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - FL, 1972-1977 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Freeman, Herb, 1971-1977 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Friedman, Joyce, 1971-1973 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - GA, 1971-1977 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Galaska, Barbra A., 1097-1973 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - GE-GL, 1971-1977 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Gehani, Narain, 1973-1977 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Gillespie, C. J., 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - GM-GO, 1971-1977 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Gortler Correspondence, 1954-1965 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Goldring, Gvirol, 1968-1970 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Gotlieb, Professor C. C., 1972-1976 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - GR, 1971-1977 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Griffith, Beluer C., 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Grosch, H. R. J., 1975-1977 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - GU, 1971-1977 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Gumb, Raymond, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Guggenheim Award Applic., 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - HA, 1971-1977 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Hansen, Brinch Per, 975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Hartmanis, Juris, 1971-1977 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Hays, David G., 1970-1977 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - HE-HJ, 1971-1977 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Henssler and Fucyman, 1973-1976 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - HO, 1971-1977 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Hollister, Irene, 1970-1977 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - I, 1971-1977 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - IndeLex Corporation, 1982-1984 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Information Systems Correspondence, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Information Systems - (Liou, J. H.), 1976 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Information Systems, (Yao, Subas, and Kashyap), 1976 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - INSPEC material, 1969-1975 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - J, 1971-1977 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Jackson NSF 70, 1970-1972 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Jackson, David M., 1969-1972 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Johnson, W. N. Recommendations, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - K-KLI, 1971-1977 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Karch, Fred - CDI, 1973-1975 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Karlgren, Hans, 1969-1976 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Karlstrom, Karl V., 1970-1974 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Karp, Raquel, 1973-1976 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Kellington, M. R., 1969-1976 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Kerchner, Marcia, 1971-1976 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Kettler, Jack F., 1970-1972 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - KN-KO, 1971-1977 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Kochen, Manfied, 1970-1977 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - KR, 1971-1973 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Lazar, P., 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Lesk, M. E., 1969-1975 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Library Board, 1974-1977 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Library Board, 1971-1975 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Library Committee, 1966-1970 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Lynn, M. S., 1970-1977 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Lyons, William W., 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Madden, J. D., 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Mallow, Carl S., 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - M-Maynard, 1971-1977 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - MC, 1971-1977 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - McGraw-Hill Book Company, 1967-1976 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - MEL-MUE, 1971-1977 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Miller, Gormly, 1976-2977 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Mineka, F., 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Minker, Jack, 1970-1977 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Moser, Andreas, 1969-1976 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Murray, Daniel, 1969-1974 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - N, 1971-1977 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Nance, Richard E., 1970-1977 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - NATIS - Correspondence, 1974-1977 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Needham, Wilson K., 1969-1977 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - O, 1971-1977 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Oram, Robert W., 1970 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - P, 1970-1977 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Painter, Dr. Ann, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Pollock, Donald K., 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Pratt, V., 1969-1971 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Prentice-Hall, 1970-1975 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Publishers - Correspondence with miscellaneous, 1966-1975 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Q, 1971-1975 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - R-RI, 1971-1977 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Raben, Joseph - Computers and the Humanities, 1970-1976 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Ralston, Anthony - AMC, 1968-1977 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Ralston - Encyclopedia of Computer Science, 1971-1976 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Ralston, Taxonomy, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - R & D Press, 1973-1976 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Revens, Lee, 1969-1975 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Rieger, Charles J. III, 1975-2977 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Rieger, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - RO, 1967-1977 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - SA, 1970-1977 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Sammet, Jean - ACM, 1972-1976 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - SC-Schuler, 1972-1977 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Schneider, H.J., 1970-1974 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Schneider H.J. (cont), 1973-1977 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Schultz-Scott, 1971-1977 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Science (includes Ringe corres.), 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - SE-SK, 1971-1977 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Sienko, Michael J., 1970 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Sigir mail, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Sigir, 1975-1981 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Sigir, 1980-1982 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Sigir, 1981-1983 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - SL-SO, 1970-1977 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Speightm, Frank Y., 1969 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - SP-ST, 1970-1977 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Stewart, Ileen, 1971-1977 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - SU, 1971-1977 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Swiss Letter, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Switzerland, 1983-1985 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - T, 1969-1977 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Tenney. R.L., 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Tompkins, Howard E., 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - U, 1969-1977 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - UNESCO - all correspondence (F. Gallo), 1970 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - V, 1970-1977 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Veaner, Allen B., 1970-1974 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - VLDB (very large database), San Fransisco, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - WA, 1970-1977 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - WE, 1970-1977 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Wegner, Peter, 1970-1977 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Weiss, Stephen, 1971-1975 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Weiss, Dr. Eric A, 1969-1977 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Weissberg, Alfred, 1971-1973 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - WH-WIN, 1969-1977 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Wienderhold, 1987-1992 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Wigington, Dr. Reynold, 1969-1972 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - NAS Committee Notes, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Willenbrock, Dr. F. Karl, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Williamson, Robert (Skip), 1970-1977 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Wimmers, Drs. W.H., 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - WIR, 1970-1977 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Wolfson, Seymour, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Wong, Jin Kue, 1975-1977 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Wormley, Sheryl (ASIS Admin. Secy.), 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Y, 1969-1977 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Yang, Hubert, 1975-1977 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Youtis, Marshall, 1969-1977 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Yu, Clement, 1972-1977 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Z, 1971-1977 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Zumoff, Joel, 1970-1973 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Additional Letters, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence re: G. S. and others pubs., request for reprints, profess. orgs., reviews, conferences, 1977-1979 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence; National Endowment for the Humanities, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - G. S. Filing (alphabetical), 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Corespondence, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Apr.-Aug. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1981
  - Sept. 1981- (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Mar. 1982
  - Correspondence, July 1982 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Oct. 1982 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, May-Dec. 1983 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Nov.-Dec. 1983 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Jan.-My 1984 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, May 1984 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, June 1986-Mar,1987 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Mar.-June 1987 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, June-Sept. 1987 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Oct. 1987-May 1988 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Corresondence, Oct. 1987-May 1988 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - A - Correspondence (alphabetical), 1990-1992 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Coorespondence, 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Corespondence, 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Corespondence, 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - A - Correspondence (alphabetical), 1991-1995 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, 1991-199 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Letter Need to Answer, May 1990 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Information regarding other Univ. departmants, undergraduate and graduate, in research, etc., 1973-1977 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - CS 635 Spring, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Course Evaluation 435, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - CS 409 - Fall, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - CS 409 - Fall, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 45)
- Series III - Professional Papers
  - Proposals - Ed Fox, ACM TISR, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Proposals - Advanced Models for Information Retrieval, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - ARPA Proposal, 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Proposal, 1979-1981 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - CER Proposal, 1990-1991 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Proposals - Cornell Workshop Report, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - DARPA Proposal, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Proposal, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Request for Proposals for an Integrated Library System for Cornell University Libraries, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Application for Public Health Service: Award or Grant, 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - NIH Proposal, 1972-1977 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - NIH, 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - NSF Proposal, Jan. 1976-Dec. 1977 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - NSF Proposal - Advanced Info. Retrieval Models and Theory, Aug. 1986-July, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - NIH AP (Array Processor) Proposal, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - NSF - Lee G. Burchinel, 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - NSF Proposal, June 1976-May 1978 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - NSF Proposal - A Catalog of Verified Information Retrieval Software, Jan. 1977-Dec.1978 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - NSA Proposal, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - NSF Final Report IST 83 16166, 1983-1987 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - NSF - IST 83 16166, 1983-1986 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - NSF - IRI 87 02735, 1986-1988 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - NSF - 87 02735 Final Report, 1987-1990 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - NSF - 87 02738 Interface Forms, 1987-1989 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - NSF 89 - Annual Report, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - NSF - IRI 93 00124, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - NSF - IRI 93 00124, 1993-1995 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - NSF Proposal, 1989-1993 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - NSF Equipment Proposal, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Proposal to the Naval Research Office, 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - NSF - File Structuring and Information Retrieval for Large Full-Text Libraries, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - NIH Grants, 1981-1986 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Atherton, Pauline, 1976-1973 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - NSF Grant - IRI 87 02735, 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Switzerland Grants, 1984-1986 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence to and from Prof. Salton with Linda P. Rask, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Final Report Equipment Grant, 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - NSF Proposal, Apr. 30, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - NIH LM 00704-01+02, Account No. U07-2110; Operating Statement and Payroll, Feb. 28, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - NIH LM 00704-01+02, Acount No U07-2110; Voucher Payroll, Account Analysis, and Trial Balance, Feb. 28, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - NIH 8317, 1970-1972 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - NSF 8308, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - NSF 8306, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - NSF GJ-314, Account No. U07-8306; Operating Statement and Payroll, Prior to Jan. 1971 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - NSF GJ-314, Account No. U07-8306; Voucher Payroll, Account Analysis, Trial Balance, Proir to Jan. 1971 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - NSF GJ-314, U07-8306, July-Dec. 1972, also Jan. 1973 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - NSF GN-750 U07 2102, Operating Statements, Apr. 15, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - NSF, July-Dec. 1967 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Paid Bills to appear on Op. Stmt. - 8306, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - ONR - M. Denicoff, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - U07-8323 - GJ 43505, ending summary, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Proposal, Progress Report, 1987-1989 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Summary Activities and Research, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Annual Reports, 1965-1967 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Annual Reports, 1969-1971 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Annual Reports, 1972-1975 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Annual Reports by other than Salton, 1982-1986 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Annual Reports by other than Salton, 1986-1988 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Annual Reports, 1988-1994 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Annual Report, Music Dept., 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - NSF Research Report, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - TR 5 - Automatic Content Analysis in Information Retrieval, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - TR 6 - Automated language processing, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - TR 11 - A Comparison between Manual and Automatic Indexing Methods, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - TR 12 - Use of Stand. Doc. Data in Auto. Info. Dissemination, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - TR 17 Interactive Search and Retrieval Methods Using Auto. Info. Displays, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - TR 17 - Evaluation of Interactive Search and Retrieval Methods Using Automatic Information Displays, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - TR 25 - Relevance Assessments and Retrieval System Evaluation, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - TR 29 - Dynamic File Organization and Heuristic Search Strategies in Information Retrieval, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - TR 36 - Automatic Text Analysis, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - TR 39 - Evaluation Problems in Interactive Information Retrieval, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - TR 40 - Interactive Information Retrieval, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - TR 67 - The "Generality" Effect and the Retrieval Evaluation for Large Collections, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - TR 115 - A New Comparison Between Conventional Indexing (MEDLARS) and Automatic Text Processing (SMART) [Self-Monitoring Analysis and Reporting Technology], 1971 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - TR 117 - New Approaches to Automatic Data Processing, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - TR 121 - Dynamic Document Processing, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - TR - CACM, Dynamic Document Processing, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - TR 138 - Proposal for a Dynamic Library, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - TR 139 - Automatic Processing of Current Affairs Queries, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - TR 153; TR 154 - On the Development of Info. Science; also Info. Processing Letters, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Center for Applied Linguistics, Language Research in Progress 5", 1973 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - TR 173 - On the Specification of Term Values in Automatic Indexing, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - TR 188 - Contribution to the Theory of Indexing, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - TR 203 - A Theory of Indexing, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - TR 203 - A Theory of Indexing, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - TR 208 - A Theory of Term Importance in Automatic Text Analysis, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 2-3)
  - TR 218 - A Vector Space Model for Automatic Indexing, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 4-5)
  - TR 232 - Precision Weighing, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 6-7)
  - TR 247 - On the Role of Words and Phrases in Automatic Text Analysis, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 8-9)
  - TR 240 - The Information Revolution - Myth or Reality, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - TR 249 - Effective Information Retrieval Using Term Accuracy, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - TR 253 - Automatic Indexing Using Term Discrimination and Precision Measurements, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - TR 261 - The Effectiveness of the Thesaurus Method in Automatic Information Retrieval, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - TR 262 (revised) - A Comparison of Term Value Measurements for Automatic Indexing, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 14-15)
  - TR 268 - Cataloging Software Package for Automatic Processing, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - TR 292 - Effective Automatic Indexing Using Term Addition and Deletion, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 17-18)
  - TR 295 - Clustered File Generation and its Application to Computer Science Taxonomies, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - TR 299 - Generation and Search of Clustered Files, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 2-4)
  - TR 309 - A Computer Science View Obtained by Automatic Document Processing, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - TR 439 - Parallel Computations in Information Retrieval, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - TR 511 - Extended Boolean Information Retrieval, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 7)